So today this happened with me on the shoot, it happens like this,
I go for the shoot early in the morning which
we had to do on the road, oh brother it is
very difficult to shoot on the road, there is so much traffic jam,
but still we did the shoot and while
shooting we met our cute
little fans, after that Chet and I go out to
eat the favorite thing of girls which is golgappas and after quickly
eating golgappas we leave for the school shoot
brother there is only one day but we have to
attend a lot of shoots so
we are quickly shooting when suddenly
another of our little fans comes and after taking a
photo with him we leave for the school
shoot and on the shoot there is a bicycle which we borrow from the
labourers working nearby at home,
oh brother you will have to borrow it,
and then while I am shooting then this happens
with me,
friend you are looking at the camera, go go, bye bye
brother a blackbird came straight and fell, I don't know
how Kannu, did you see that, now we are
fixing the blackboard, brother how many times did it happen, thank God I was saved  with
kindness